
Deck.create(name:"Nighthawk Trivia")
Card.create(question: "What is a nighthawk's primary food source?", answer: "insects",deck_id:1)
Card.create(question: "True or false?  Nighthawks are closely related to hawks.", answer: "false",deck_id:1)
Card.create(question: "True or false?  Nighthawks make nests.", answer: "false",deck_id:1)
Card.create(question: "Where do Common Nighthawks spend the winter?", answer: "South America",deck_id:1)
Card.create(question: "True or false?  Bullbat is another name for the Common Nighthawk.", answer: "true",deck_id:1)

Deck.create(name:"Otter Trivia")
Card.create(question: "What is an otter's primary food source?", answer: "fish",deck_id:2)
Card.create(question: "True or false? Otters spend the majority of their time on land.", answer: "true",deck_id:2)
Card.create(question: "How many species of otters are there?", answer: "13",deck_id:2)
Card.create(question: "True of false? Otters are native to Australia.", answer: "false",deck_id:2)
Card.create(question: "True or false? Otters make and use tools.", answer: "true",deck_id:2)
Card.create(question: "In years, what is the average life span of an otter in the wild?", answer: "10",deck_id:2)

Deck.create(name:"Raccoon Trivia")
Card.create(question: "What is a male raccoon called?", answer: "boar",deck_id:3)
Card.create(question: "What is a female raccoon called?", answer: "sow",deck_id:3)
Card.create(question: "Are raccoons herbivorous, carnivorous, or omnivorous?", answer: "omnivorous",deck_id:3)
Card.create(question: "True or false?  Raccoons are nocturnal.", answer: "true",deck_id:3)
Card.create(question: "True or false?  Raccoons hibernate.", answer: "false",deck_id:3)
Card.create(question: "True or false?  Raccoons can run at speeds up to 15 miles per hour.", answer: "true",deck_id:3)
